question_data = [
  {"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Indie Game Development Studio Cing, developers of Hotel Dusk and Last Window, went bankrupt on March 1st, 2010.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Greenland is covered with grass and Iceland covered with ice.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"San Marino is the only country completely surrounded by another country.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"History","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The United States was a member of the League of Nations.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Film","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the original script of &quot;The Matrix&quot;, the machines used humans as additional computing power instead of batteries.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"A scientific study on peanuts in bars found traces of over 100 unique specimens of urine.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In &quot;Sonic Adventure&quot;, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"General Knowledge","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"&quot;Ananas&quot; is mostly used as the word for Pineapple in other languages.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The ultimate phrase used by Pharah from Overwatch is: &quot;Justice rains from above!&quot;","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Board Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"There is a Donald Trump Board Game, which was made in 1989.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Computers","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The NVidia GTX 1080 gets its name because it can only render at a 1920x1080 screen resolution.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Celebrities","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Marilyn Monroe was born on July 1, 1926.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime & Manga","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Kiznaiver is an adaptation of a manga.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Geography","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Hungary is the only country in the world beginning with H.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Video Games","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In the &quot;S.T.A.L.K.E.R.&quot; series, the Freedom faction wishes to destroy the supernatural area known as  &quot;the Zone&quot;.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Music","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"In 1993, Prince changed his name to an unpronounceable symbol because he was unhappy with his contract with Warner Bros.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science & Nature","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Not including false teeth; A human has two sets of teeth in their lifetime.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Science: Mathematics","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"An isosceles triangle has two sides of equal length as opposed to three.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"category":"Animals","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"Rabbits are carnivores.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"category":"Entertainment: Books","type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","question":"The Harry Potter series of books, combined, are over 1,000,000 words in length.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]}
]
